Amanda Sealshaw in today's goes to great security.
A recent concert in Georgia turned into a disappearing act.
Tyrese was in the middle of belting out his song,
Why You Wanna Act Like That?
When a security guard walked over and warned him that there was a process server,
you know, the person who like gives you papers to get sued.
There was a process server at the show without skipping a beat.
Tyrese bolted stage right.
He managed to yell out a quick, I love you guys.
But all the audience saw was ass and elbows.
And the words of JB Smooth ain't nothing faster than that.
But big up to that security guard.
If understanding the assignment was a person,
spotting out a process server is like a condiment in a cannon's house.
I mean, it's very, very difficult to find.
All right, today's goes to bad recruiting tactics.
The Miami Beach Police Department proudly introduced their latest recruitment tactic,
a $250,000 Rolls-Royce patrol car.
Because, you know, nothing says protect and serve like luxury wheels.
Now, they claim that the car has been lent to them.
So it's not going to cost the taxpayers anything.
But still, instead of attracting offers who genuinely want to make a difference,
they're banking on anyone who grew up with watching like cash money videos,
being like, you know, bang, bang.
Nonetheless, it just, again, exemplifies how out of touch the police force are from the community
and from actually being something to take seriously.